manar elsheref

Egypt



eng_manar_bme@yahoo.com



linkedin.com/in/manar-elsheref-48980130

Summary

Experienced Senior Web Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in Search Engine Optimization (SEO), PHP, WordPress, jQuery, and Adobe Photoshop, Aftereffects.

Strong information technology professional with a distnict focused in systems and biomedical engineering from Cairo university- faculty of engineering.

Experience



Senior Web Developer, web admin

RoayaMas

May 2012 - Present (9 years 2 months +)

Senior Web Developer, Web Admin

GPNet

Aug 2007 - Dec 2009 (2 years 5 months)

c# senior instructor

Cairo university- cuhtc Center Oct 2004 - 2007 (3 years 3 months)

instructor

cuhtc

2003 - 2006 (4 years)

Education



Cairo university- faculty of engineering

distnict, systems and biomedical engineering

Skills

```
jQuery • CSS • Web Development • MySQL • ASP.NET • C# • Microsoft SQL Server •
JavaScript • SEO • PHP4/5
```